Guide to the Jimmy De Sana Papers 1954-1997 (bulk 1977-1990) MSS 202
© 2010 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Negatives by theme
  - Subseries H: Portraits
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Smith, Patti; Erasers - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 56)
    - Title: (Box 56)
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Soho Saturday, Alman, Richard Bernstein - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Squirrels - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Steffanotti, Robert / "Gigi Williams, R.S., and Anya" labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Sullivan, Billy with Cortez-Eins, Crispo - Armyan - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 56)
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Notations by de Sana
      Process: Letter-Sized Envelope
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Number of Items: 270
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Teenage Head and Mars - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Teenage Jesus and the Jerks - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Trebay, Guy; R.S. and Ramos, Jose - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 56)
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Warhol, Andy with Victor Hugo (also labeled Halston’s boyfriend and Jose)
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Warhol, Andy
    - Title: (Box 57)
    - Title: (Box 57)
      Description: Unidentified Men and Women
      Number of Items: 910
  - Subseries I: Reproductions of Other Artists' Work
    - Title: (Box 58)
      Description: Sculpture and Painting Documentation for Reproduction
      Number of Items: 1128
    - Title: (Box 58)
      Description: Horse
    - Title: (Box 58)
      Description: Ray Johnson collage
    - Title: (Box 58)
      Description: Rephotographed victims
  - Subseries J: Travel
    - Title: (Box 58)
      Description: Cadsden, Alabama
    - Title:, 1972 (Box 58)
      Description: Chicago, Illinois
    - Title: (Box 58)
      Description: Christmas
    - Title:, 1972 (Box 58)
      Description: Cleveland, Ohio
    - Title: (Box 58)
      Description: Gregory Battcock and Robert Stefanotty, Italy
    - Title: (Box 58)
      Description: Jamaica
    - Title:, 1973 (Box 58)
      Description: "Natalie and Ted Stilkins House"
    - Title:, 1973 (Box 58)
      Description: New Hampshire
    - Title: (Box 58)
      Description: New Jersey
    - Title: (Box 58)
      Description: Palm Beach
      Number of Items: 125
    - Title:, 1971 (Box 58)
    - Title:, 1972 (Box 58)
    - Title:, 1973 (Box 58)
    - Title: (Box 58)
      Description: "Ted and Marid Stilfimo, Lion Country Safari"
      Number of Items: 95
    - Title: (Box 58)
      Description: "Travel, Atl., Palm, Nature"
      Number of Items: 45
    - Title: (Box 58)
      Description: Travel, Edwardo Hidalgo and Jimmy de Sana
    - Title: (Box 58)
      Description: Vermont
    - Title:, 1973 (Box 58)
    - Title: (Box 58)
      Description: Unidentified Travel Photography
      Number of Items: 110
  - Subseries K: Medium-format Negatives
    Series VI Subseries K contains medium format negatives which could not be integrated into the storage binders with the rest of the material because of size. Subseries K is stored separately, but organized into sub-subseries which match themes elsewhere in Series VI and should be considered of a piece with them.
    - Subseries K, Sub-subseries i: Documentation
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 73)
        Process: 2 1/4 X 2 1/4 Negative
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 73)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 73)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 73)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 74)
        Description: Painting - Marker Cones
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 74)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 74)
        Description: Sweatshirt
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 75)
        Description: Earring
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 75)
        Description: Fur Coat
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 75)
        Description: Underwear
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 75)
        Description: Tom McCabe
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 76)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 76)
        Description: Extension Chord
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 76)
    - Subseries K, Sub-subseries ii: Miscellaneous
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 77)
        Description: Labeled by JDS “Country House”
    - Subseries K, Sub-subseries iii: Portrait
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 78)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 78)
        Description: Burroughs, William, Laurie Anderson, John Giorno
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 78)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 79)
        Description: de Sana, Jimmy with Dog, and Friend
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 80)
        Description: Labeled by JDS “Richard Mock, Stewart Hitch”
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 81)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 81)
    - Subseries K, Sub-subseries iv: Reproductions of Other Artists' Work
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 82)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 83)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 84)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 85)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 86)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 87)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 88)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 89)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 90)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 91)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 92)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 93)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 94)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 95)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 96)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 97)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 98)
      - Title: (Box 60, Folder 98)
        Description: Television and reflecting pool installation
        Process: 2 1/4 X 2 1/4 Color Negative
- Series VII: Color Negatives by project
  - Subseries A: Submission
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: Anal penetration
      Process: Color Negative Film
  - Subseries B: Early Sex
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Process: 8x10 Color Negative Film
    - Title: (Box 59)
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 59)
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: Bathroom double Nude lampshade
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 59)
      Description: "Beachballs beachballs, sneakers, in a glade "
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 59)
      Description: Bed (jump) shoot
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 59)
    - Title: Bottles, 1982 (Box 59)
      Description: " Bottles "
    - Title: Celery, 1980 (Box 59)
      Description: Celery
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 59)
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 59)
    - Title: Boxes, 1980 (Box 59)
      Description: "Couple on lawn furniture “Storage Boxes” "
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 59)
      Description: "Deck Red light Two Nudes "
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 59)
      Description: "Female photographer Untitled (suit) Instant Camera"
    - Title:, 1981 (Box 59)
      Description: "Giant Beachball shoot Jimmy de Sana (and Paula Greif?) models"
    - Title: Ladder, 1980 (Box 59)
      Description: "Ladder "
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 59)
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
      Description: "Nude outside Telephone Wire shoot"
    - Title:, 1981 (Box 59)
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 59)
      Description: "Plastic Bags "
    - Title: (Box 59)
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 59)
    - Title: (Box 59)
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 59)
      Description: "Shoes (under dining table) "
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: Shoot for Nike
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: Silver Mask in Trees
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 59)
    - Title:, 1981 (Box 59)
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 59)
    - Title: Travel Bags, 1981 (Box 59)
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: Bondage Kitchen Green String
      Process: 4x5 Color Negative Film
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: Bondage red string
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: Chair shoot, Laurie Simmons
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: Chocolate Syrup, Half Body
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
      Description: "Cigarette shoot brick wall "
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
      Description: Coffee Table
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
      Description: Condom
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: Coyote
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: Eggs at Beach
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
    - Title: Fur Coat, 1979 (Box 59)
      Description: Fur Coat outside
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: Headstand
    - Title: Helmet, 1979 (Box 59)
      Description: Helmet, city
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
    - Title: (Box 59)
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
      Description: Leaves
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
      Description: Mask
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: "Nylons (Shoe) Laurie Simmons model"
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 59)
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
      Description: Pocket Book
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
      Description: "Purse Head Laurie Simmons"
    - Title: (Box 59)
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: Shoe beach
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
      Description: Tube
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
      Description: Tube (Beach)
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
      Description: Watermelon
- Series VIII: Color Negatives by theme
  Items from the Portrait theme (Subseries C) are organized by the subject's last name. Where a last name is absent slides are organized alphabetically by first name. These are followed by unidentified subjects.
  - Subseries A: Landscape
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
  - Subseries B: Miscellaneous
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: Peter Brahms designs ltd
  - Subseries C: Portrait
    - Title: (Box 59)
    - Title: (Box 59)
    - Title: (Box 59)
    - Title: (Box 59)
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: Greif, Paula
    - Title: (Box 59)
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: Harry, Debbie and Warhol, Andy
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: Lindsay, Arto
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 59)
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 59)
    - Title: (Box 59)
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: Simmons, Laurie - nephew of
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: Male Nude at swimming pool
    - Title: (Box 59)
    - Title: (Box 59)
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: de Sana, Jimmy and Bagley, Darrell wedding
    - Title: (Box 59)
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: Two boys and puppies
    - Title: (Box 59)
      Description: Unknown man
- Series IX: Half-tone triplicate reproductions by project
  - Subseries A: Salvation
    - Title: (Box 60, Folder 99)
      Process: Half-tone
    - Title: (Box 60, Folder 100)
    - Title: (Box 60, Folder 101)
    - Title: (Box 60, Folder 102)
      Description: Blowfish
- Series X: Silver Gelatin Contact Sheets by project
  - Subseries A: 101 Nudes
    - Title: (Box 61)
      Description: 101 Nudes Contact Sheets
      Process: Silver Gelatin Contact Sheet
  - Subseries B: Submission
    - Title:, 1978-1979 (Box 61)
      Description: Submission Contact Sheets
    - Title:, 1978-1979 (Box 62)
    - Title:, 1978-1979 (Box 63)
  - Subseries C: Early Sex
    - Title: (Box 64)
    - Title: (Box 64)
  - Subseries D: $bfat
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Bubble Gum
    - Title: (Box 64)
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Pants, dog
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: With Jimmy Jr. on Beach
  - Subseries E: $dobjects
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Balloons
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: "Collage variations Popcorn "
    - Title: (Box 64)
  - Subseries F: Auto-Portrait
    - Title: (Box 64)
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Birds, Cardboard
    - Title: (Box 64)
    - Title: (Box 64)
    - Title: (Box 64)
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Scar
    - Title: (Box 64)
    - Title: (Box 64)
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: "With Jimmy Jr. Smoke Cowboy"
  - Subseries G: Cut Up
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Cut Piece: Pendant and various Rupert Smith
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Cut Piece
  - Subseries H: Salvation
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: "Cap oval scratch Collage Parka, Condom, Powder, Playmoney"
    - Title: (Box 64)
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Collage variations including Guitar
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Collage variations including Gym Shorts
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Collage variations including Letter O
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Various Powder
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: "Young boys Faith in the Cosmos"
- Series XI: Silver Gelatin Contact Sheets by theme
  - Subseries A: Events
    - Title: (Box 64)
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Anya Phillips, James Chance White
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Art
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Art Exhibition Space
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Atlana
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Diego Cortez
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Drag Queen
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Drag Queens
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Jackie Curtis
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Museum of Broadcasting
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Man with Monitor
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Nam June Paik
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Puerto Rican demonstration
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Sol le Witt Opening
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Street Fair
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Thom Cote, Anya Phillips
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Thom Cote, Richard Hell
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Unidentified Events
  - Subseries B: Landscape
    - Title:, 1978 (Box 65)
      Description: Landscape series
  - Subseries C: Miscellaneous
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Auto Art cake
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: "Darrell Bagley Jimmy de Sana"
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Dog from Submission
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Dummy on Ceiling
    - Title: (Box 65)
    - Title: (Box 65)
    - Title: (Box 65)
    - Title: (Box 65)
  - Subseries D: Portrait
    - Title: (Box 65)
    - Title: (Box 65)
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Arrest
    - Title: (Box 65)
    - Title: (Box 65)
    - Title:, 1988 (Box 65)
      Description: Bomb Magazine Staff photographed for Vanity Fair
    - Title: (Box 65)
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Brockis, Victor
    - Title: (Box 65)
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Churicova, Inna and Gleb Panfilov
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 65)
    - Title: (Box 65)
    - Title: (Box 65)
    - Title: (Box 65)
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Crutchfield, Robin
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Cutrone, Ron (labeled on Negatives by JDS "Sebastian"nie
    - Title: (Box 66)
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: de Sana, Jimmy; Laurie Simmons
    - Title: (Box 66)
    - Title: (Box 66)
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Delilght, Duca
    - Title: (Box 66)
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: GiGi
    - Title: (Box 66)
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Hidalgo, Eddie
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Hidalgo, Eddie Christmas
    - Title: (Box 66)
    - Title: (Box 66)
    - Title: (Box 66)
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Mars and Teenage Head
    - Title: (Box 66)
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: McCormick, Carlo and Tessa Hughes-Freeland
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Mcdermitt, David and David McGuff, Laurie Simmons, Darrell Bagely, and Jimmy de Sana
    - Title: (Box 66)
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Nervous Breakdown; Voidoids
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Nylon, Judy; Jimmy de Sana, Thom Cote
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Phillips, Anya; James Chance White
    - Title: (Box 66)
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Ramos, Jose, also labeled Victor Hugo (Halston’s boyfriend)
    - Title: (Box 66)
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Ron (labeled on Negatives by JDS "Sebastian"
    - Title: (Box 66)
    - Title: (Box 67)
    - Title: (Box 67)
    - Title: (Box 67)
    - Title: (Box 67)
      Description: Smith, Patti
    - Title: (Box 67)
      Description: Smith, Patti Eric and Robin Lee,
    - Title: (Box 67)
      Process: Silver Gelatin Contact Sheet Fragment
    - Title: (Box 67)
    - Title: (Box 67)
    - Title: (Box 67)
      Description: Talking Heads, Unidentified Band
    - Title: (Box 67)
      Description: Teenage Head
    - Title: (Box 67)
    - Title: (Box 67)
    - Title: (Box 67)
      Description: Warhol, Andy; Robert Stefanotty
    - Title: (Box 67)
    - Title: (Box 67)
      Description: White, James Chance and Lydia Lunch
    - Title: (Box 67)
      Description: Unknown Band
    - Title: (Box 67)
      Description: Unidentified Subjects
    - Title: (Box 68)
  - Subseries E: Reproductions of Other Artists' Work
    - Title: (Box 68)
  - Subseries F: Travel
    - Title: (Box 68)
- Series XII: Pat Hearn Materials
  Clippings, papers and color transparency slides collected by the Pat Hearn Gallery. The clippings are organized by date; when the date is unknown the documents are placed at the end of the subseries.
  - Subseries A: Color Transparency Slides
    - Title: (Box 69)
      Description: Documentation of work, ordered as found 1983 - 87 desending
      Process: Color Transparency Slides
      Number of Items: 470
    - Title: (Box 70)
      Description: Documentation of work, ordered as found 1979 -82 desending
      Number of Items: 565
    - Title: (Box 71)
      Description: Installation shots, 101 Nudes, Submission documentation, ordered as found
      Number of Items: 308
  - Subseries B: Papers and clippings organized by Pat Hearn Gallery
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 103)
      Flash Art review - February 1980
    - Title:, 1981 (Box 72, Folder 104)
      Roberta Smith review, Art in America - January 1981
    - Title:, 1981 (Box 72, Folder 105)
      New Figuration in America, New Directions Catalogue - 1981
    - Title:, 1981 (Box 72, Folder 106)
      New Voices, "6 Photographers" - 1981
    - Title:, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 107)
      "Big Car Show" catalogue - May 1985
    - Title:, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 108)
      Wolkenkratzer Art Journal, Diego Cortez/ de Sana interview - Oct 1986
    - Title:, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 109)
      Village Voice review - 24 February 1987
    - Title:, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 110)
      108 Review - January 1988
      NY Times review - 29 January 1988
      Art in America review - November 1988
    - Title:, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 111)
      "Mirroring Enigmas," essay by G. Roger Denison, Arts Magazine - May 1989
    - Title:, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 112)
      Journal of Contemporary Art, Laurie Simmons on Jimmy de Sana - Summer 1990
    - Title:, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 113)
      Jimmy de Sana obituary, Art World - September 1990
    - Title:, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 114)
      Two Arts Festival of Atlanta reviews - September 1990
    - Title:, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 115)
      NY Times Review, 101 Nudes - 4 January 1991
    - Title:, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 116)
      Print Collector's Newsletter, containing "Grotesque Photography," by Brooks Adams - January 1991
    - Title:, 1992, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 117)
      The Sexual Self review - October 1992
      Press Release PHG - September 1995
    - Title:, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 118)
      NY Times Review - 29 September 1995
    - Title:, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 119)
      Artforum review - November 1995
    - Title:, 1998 (Box 72, Folder 120)
      Art Resources Transfer Correspondence with Pat Hearn Gallery - November 1998
    - Title:, 2000 (Box 72, Folder 121)
      Press release and New York Times review, Bob Nickas 'D' at Sandrea Gering - March 2000
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 122)
      Art in America review - date unknown
      American Photographer review - date unknown
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 123)
      de Sana resume on Pat Hearn Letterhead
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 124)
      de Sana resumes on Pat Hearn Letterhead
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 125)
      PHG letterhead
- Series XIII: Ephemera
  Papers and clippings collected by the Jimmy De Sana estate. In subseries A, materials are arranged alphabetically by folder description. In subseries B, materials are retained in the original order given by Jimmy De Sana. There is one oversize item from this subseries, a record sleeve for James White and the Blacks, stored in box 78. It originally came last in Jimmy De Sana's sequence of ephemera.
  - Subseries A: Papers and clippings found throughout the Jimmy De Sana estate
    - Title:, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 126)
      Description: American Foundation for AIDS research flyer, AIDS quilt photo
      Number of Items:
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 127)
      Description: Birthday Card made by Janet Stein, unknown addressee
    - Title:, 1988, 1983 (Box 72, Folder 128)
      Description: Book of Nine, Gary Stephan - two small publications - Quotations from JDS
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 129)
      Description: Candid photos, Kenny Goodman
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 130)
      Description: Colored Gels
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 131)
      Description: Color Photocopies
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 132)
      Description: Image Scavenger Catalog
    - Title:, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 133)
      Description: Invoice and financial papers
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 134)
      Description: JDS notes for Art Resources transfer book
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 135)
      Description: JDS notes on exposure times
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 136)
      Description: Pamphlet, "The Paintings of John Hull"
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 137)
      Description: NY Rocker Correspondence
    - Title:, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 138)
      Description: Envelope; Mrs. A. J. De Sana to Jimmy De Sana
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 139)
      Description: Photocopied portrait
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 140)
      Description: Postcards: Image Bank, Rome, Renzoni, Cortez, Patrick McMullan, John Brill, Man Ray
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 141)
      Description: Postcards: Wrongrong, JDS 1988, Seashells, Sweatshirt
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 142)
      Description: Stills from "Material Interchange"
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 143)
      Description: Submission Cover
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 144)
      Description: Thank you note
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 145)
      Description: Wedding photo, printed painting
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 146)
      Description: What's My Line? Game; John Barrymore, Gloria Swanson photos
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 147)
      Description: Holograms
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 148)
      Description: Reviews: Artforum, Artnews
  - Subseries B: Papers and clippings compiled by Jimmy De Sana
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 149)
      Zoom article
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 150)
      Anderson-Burroughs-Giorno record cover
      Art forum ad - October 1982
      SoHo Hews cover Salvador Dali/ Lene Lovich - 2 April 1980
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 151)
      Soho News cover K. Anger - 16 July 1980
      Istoe article on William Burroughs - 30 May 1984
      New Voices 2 (4 pages)
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 152)
      David Bourdon jacket
      Androgyny in Art tearsheets
      New Figuration in America papers
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 153)
      Big Car Show catalogue
      Bomb "Cowboy Hat" - Summer 1985
      SoHo News cover Laurie Anderson - 5 November 1980
      Eye cover Billy Idol - Dec/Jan 1983
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 154)
      SoHo News centerfold - 29 Novemeber 1979
      Frigidaire article - September 1981
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 155)
      American Photo- March/April 1993
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 156)
      Danceteria ad
      New York Times review - 29 January 1988
      Press clippings - 16 March 1988
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 157)
      Savvy article - July 1988
      Neo York catalogue
      Scanagraph info
      The Face clipping - November 1986
      Omni letter
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 158)
      New Times clippings - 8 January 1979
      Studio Trisorio ad